dressupgirl.net 2017-12-22

# Privacy Policy - Free online games for Girls and Kids

To play games in DressupGirl.net you do not need to give up any personal information.  
When you register as a member, we collect Personal Information including your email address, first name, last name, and birthday, or any information that is voluntarily provided by you.  
We maintain log files which contain IP addresses. An IP address is a numeric address that is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. We do not link IP addresses to personal information. In general, we only use log files to monitor traffic on our Websites and to troubleshoot technical problems. In the event of abuse, however, we may block certain IP addresses.   
We use Personal Information primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving the website DressupGirl.net. We do not send newsletters or mass emails  
We have no control over third parties to whom you may give Personal Information through the use of DressupGirl.net.   
From time to time, we also use the information you provide about yourself or others to inform you of additions or improvements to the DressupGirl.net services as well as conduct member surveys in order to improve our service.  
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways or for reasons unrelated to the ones described above without also providing an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**WELCOME TO DRESSUPFGIRL.NET AND THANK YOU FOR VISITING!**
